testo.com 2010-08-22

# Testo, USA - Privacy Policy

We at testo Inc. are happy you chose to visit our website and for your interest in our company and products. We take the protection of your privacy and data very seriously. The information given to us during your visit to our website is handled with the greatest confidentiality and in accordance with legal regulations. We only collect personal information that is voluntarily given. Personal information is used only when you have expressly stated your agreement. Personal information is only used to fulfill your requests and requirements, e.g. within the context of a service, a survey, a sweepstakes, or an inquiry. You can retract your consent to the use and storage of your personal information at any time. All data that you disclose is stored and handled exclusively within our company. Under no circumstance will any of your personal information be shared with a third party without your consent. Furthermore, we have taken precautionary measures to block unwanted access by third parties to stored data.

Should you wish to have data corrected or removed, or have any additional questions or suggestions, please fill out our Contact Form.

#### Limitation of Liability:

The information in this website is reviewed and updated on a regular basis, however the information provided is not legally binding and testo Inc. reserves the right to modify and or make amendments to the information provided, herefore any responsibility for the accuracy and completeness is excluded.

#### Issued by:

testo, Inc.  
40 White Lake Road  
Sparta, NJ 07871

Managing Director: Marko Bruinsma

Toll Free: 800-227-0729  
Ph.: 862-354-5001  
Fax: 862-354-5020  
Email: [info@testo.com](mailto:info@testo.com)
